Guide to the New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia MC.234
New York University Archives
New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia
circa 1900-2013
New York University Archives
Leonard N. Stern School of Business
MC.234
30 linear feet in 30 record cartons
571 items
The New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia contains approximately 571 three-dimensional objects discovered by New York University facility workers in a crawl space under the auditorium of the Leonard N. Stern School of Business. The collection consists of pig figurines made of various materials ranging from glass, porcelain, and cloth, to soap and marzipan. Some objects are utilitarian, including piggy banks, salt and pepper shakers, ashtrays, gravy boats, pitchers, and jewelry boxes. The objects likely date between 1900 and 2013, and originated from all over the world.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Provenance unknown. The accession number associated with this transfer from the New York University Leonard N. Stern School of Business is 13.019.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into series and sub-series based upon the complexity and the material of the objects.
The arrangement of the collection is as follows:
Series I: Single Pig Figurines
Subseries I A: Plain, Ceramic Pig Figurines
Subseries I B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Human-Like Traits
Subseries I C: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Floral Designs
Subseries I D: Glass Pig Figurines
Subseries I E: Wooden Pig Figurines
Subseries I F: Plastic and Rubber Pig Figurines
Subseries I G: Cloth Pig Figurines
Subseries I H: Metal Pig Figurines
Subseries I I: Stone Pig Figurines
Subseries I J: Marzipan, Soap, and Clay Pig Figurines
Series II: Complex Pig Figurines and Sets
Subseries II A: Plain, Ceramic Pig Sets
Subseries II B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Humans
Subseries II C: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Human-Like Traits
Subseries II D: Glass, Stone, and Plastic Pig Sets
Subseries II E: Wooden Pig Sets
Subseries II F: Metal Pig Sets
Series III: Utilitarian Objects
Subseries III A: Ashtrays
Subseries III B: Salt and Pepper Shakers
Subseries III C: Gravy Boats, Salad Dressing Bottles, and Creamers
Subseries III D: Pitchers
Subseries III E: Beer Mugs, Shot Glasses, and Bottle Openers
Subseries III F: Plates and Cups
Subseries III G: Cookie Jars and Other Food Containers
Subseries III H: Piggy Banks
Subseries III I: Wall Hangings and Artwork
Subseries III J: Ornaments
Subseries III K: Ceramic Containers for Jewelry
Subseries III L: Mixed Objects
Historical Note
The New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia was discovered by university facility workers in a crawl space under the auditorium of the Leonard N. Stern School of Business. The creator and donor of the collection are unknown. Stamps, labels, inscriptions, and crests on individual objects indicate that the assembled collection originates from all over the world, from regions of the United States, from parts of Asia, and from several countries in Europe.
Custodial History
According to a May 12, 2013 New York Times article by Edna Ishayik “Little Pigs, Little Pigs, Let Us In On Your History,” New York University facility workers discovered the collection in a crawl space under the auditorium of the Leonard N. Stern School of Business. Paul Affuso, an associate dean at the business school, stated the collection may have been a gift to the undergraduate college, given by an alumna who had collected them during her lifetime as a hobby. A December 27, 1993 Chicago Tribune article “For some College Gifts, Even the Thought May Not Count,” by Frank James suggests that a male donor and his family gifted the collection.
Under Affuso’s direction, the collection was moved to a supply closet in the business school’s Tisch Hall. The objects were unpacked and placed on bookshelves, where they remained for a few years. Professional movers were called by the facilities team to consolidate the collection, although a few figurines were pulled from the closet to show a reporter back in April 2013. It is unclear how long the boxes remained in the closet or if they were stored in another location prior to being transferred to the University Archives.
Scope and Contents Note
The New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia contains approximately 571 three-dimensional objects. The majority of the collection consists of pig figurines of various sizes crafted from glass, porcelain, cloth, and more unconventional materials, such as soap and marzipan. The objects in this collection vary in gender, color, size, place of origin, and sometimes patterns or markings. The collection also includes utilitarian objects, such as piggy banks, salt and pepper shakers, ashtrays, gravy boats, pitchers, jewelry boxes, as well as memorabilia adorned with decorative pig motifs. The objects likely date between 1900 and 2013 and, as indicated by various stamps, labels, inscriptions, and crests, originate from the United States, parts of Europe and Asia.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Porcelain animals -- 20th century.; Porcelain animals -- 21st century.; Wood-carved figurines -- 20th century.; Wood-carved figurines -- 21st century.; Glass animals -- 20th century.; Collectibles.; Souvenirs (Keepsakes); Pigs.; Piglets.; Swine.; Sows.; Boars.; Leonard N. Stern School of Business
- Series I: Single Pig Figurines
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains figurines of individual pigs grouped into subseries based on material type and action depicted. Some figurines are of a pig's head or torso.
  - Subseries I A: Plain Ceramic Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of ceramic material.
    - Red and Yellow Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 3)
      Red and yellow ceramic pig; chipped tail and cracks present
    - Green Warthog Head, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 8)
      Green, ceramic warthog head with open mouth and tusks; damaged
    - Pig with Polka Dot Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 16)
      Very light gray ceramic pig figurine with blue polka dots; flat on one side; "M.A. Hadley" inscription on back
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 17)
      Pink, ceramic standing pig figurine with blue eyes and charcoal features
    - Female Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 18)
      Stretching ceramic female pig figurine that is gray in color with brown spots; broken foot
    - Pig with Large Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 31)
      Sitting white pig with charcoal-colored spots and large ears; ceramic
    - White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 25)
      White, ceramic pig figurine in hunched position; missing foot
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 1)
      Beige, ceramic pig figurine with charcoal-colored spots; pig is standing
    - Long Off-White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 21)
      Long, off-white, ceramic pig figurine with Beswick label on back
    - Spotted Pig Eating, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 10)
      Ceramic, pink pig with dark spots eating from a bowl
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 24)
      Ceramic, white standing pig with orange spots
    - White and Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 25)
      Ceramic, white and pink standing pig with black eyes
    - Chubby Pig with Patch, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 22)
      Ceramic, chubby, light beige pig with blue patch on back
    - Pink Female Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 22)
      Ceramic, female, standing pig figurine that is pink in color with charcoal shading
    - Resting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 35)
      Ceramic, gray, glazed pig figurine with plum shading in reclining position
    - Pig on Grass, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 18)
      Light, pink, ceramic pig sitting on a patch of dark green grass
    - Resting Female Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 4, Item 3)
      Blue, ceramic, female pig resting; figurine flat on one side
    - Pig with Splayed Legs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 4)
      Pink, ceramic pig with splayed legs
    - Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 7)
      Cow-like, black and white spotted standing pig; ceramic
    - Reddish-Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 14)
      Reddish-brown, ceramic, standing pig figurine
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 15)
      Beige, ceramic pig figurine with brown and black spots
    - White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 16)
      White, ceramic pig figurine
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 8)
      White and brown spotted, ceramic pig figurine in seated position
    - Black and Cream Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 11)
      Ceramic, standing, female pig figurine that is mostly black in color except a cream strip that runs across the neck and extends down to the front legs; Hampshire label on back although the word "Japan" is stamped on the bottom of a front leg
    - Pig with Crest, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 12)
      White, ceramic, resting pig with golden facial features and colorful back crest that reads "Clamant Nostra Tela In Regis Querela". "Woolwich Stroke of Trent" stamp on bottom.
    - Pig with Golden Features, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 13)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with golden ears and trotters in a seated position; larger version of item 15 in box 5
    - Pig with Golden Features, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 15)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with golden ears and trotters in a seated position; smaller version of item 13 in box 5
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 20)
      Pink, ceramic pig in seated position
    - Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 22)
      Standing, female, ceramic pig with floppy ears
    - Male Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 10)
      Dark brown, male, ceramic pig; tape present; broken ear and missing tail
    - Female Pig with Upturned Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 12)
      Pink, female, ceramic pig with upturned ears
    - Resting Multi-Colored Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 15)
      Ceramic, glazed, multi-colored pig in resting position; oil-like coloring
    - Resting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 19)
      Ceramic, glazed, multi-colored pig in resting position; oil-like coloring that is darker than item 15 in box 7
    - Resting Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 4)
      Light pink, ceramic pink in resting position
    - Pig with Forward Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 11)
      Light, grayish-blue, ceramic pig with forward ears
    - Round Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 15)
      Very round, ceramic, reddish-brown pig with white, black, and green pattern
    - Pig in Cup, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 19)
      Pink, ceramic pig in oversize, green cup
    - Pig with Trough and Baskets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 2)
      White, ceramic pig with blue collar sitting in front of baskets and a trough
    - Pig with Jewel Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 8)
      Beige and brown, ceramic pig with jewels for eyes
    - Pig with Gold Features, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 6)
      Blue, ceramic pig with gold features
    - Pig in Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 25)
      Pink, ceramic pig in green and orange container
    - Resting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 15)
      Red, glazed, ceramic, resting pig
    - Hollow Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 17)
      Orange, ceramic, hollow pig; Asian-inspired
    - Pig with Back Crest, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 19)
      White, ceramic pig with gold features and colorful "Wateringbury" crest on its back
    - Pig with Long Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 13)
      Pinkish-lavender, ceramic pig with long ears in a standing position
    - Pink and Blue Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 6)
      Pink and blue, ceramic, sitting pig
    - Female Multi-Colored Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 13)
      Multi-colored, ceramic, standing, female pig
    - Leaping Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 14)
      Pink, ceramic pig leaping; prominent curly tail
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 15)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with brown, green, and black spots
    - Asbury Park Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 17)
      Light beige, ceramic pig with block letters down back that read "Souvenir of Asbury Park"
    - Black and White Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 18)
      Black and white spotted, sitting, ceramic pig
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 19)
      Pink, ceramic, standing pig; separated from set
    - Brown and Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 20)
      Brown and Beige, ceramic, standing pig
    - Pig with Star Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 21)
      Reddish-brown, ceramic pig eating; star motif all over body and prominent gold tail
    - White and Light Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 22)
      White and light beige, ceramic, sitting pig
    - Pig with Blue Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 4)
      White, ceramic pig with blue eyes and pink tail and snout; pig appears to be running
    - Pig with Grid-Like Pattern, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 5)
      Pink, ceramic, standing pig with all over grid-like pattern
    - Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 7)
      Beige, ceramic, standing pig
    - Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 13)
      Cow-like, black and white pig resting; ceramic
    - Cow-Like Pig Resting, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 16)
      Cow-like, ceramic pig resting
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 21)
      White and tan spotted, ceramic pig
    - Hunched Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 22)
      Hunched, off-white, ceramic pig
    - Green and White Pig Figurine, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 6)
      Green and white, ceramic pig figurine
    - Pig with Heeled Shoe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 8)
      Pig in green heeled shoe; ceramic
    - Sitting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 18)
      Yellow, ceramic, sitting pig; chips in ceramic
    - Pink and Gray Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 19)
      Pink and gray, ceramic, standing pig
    - Light Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 20)
      Light pink, ceramic, sitting pig
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 21)
      Pink, ceramic pig with some black detailing
    - Red Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 22)
      Red, ceramic, standing pig
    - White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 24)
      White, ceramic, standing pig
    - Green Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 25)
      Green, ceramic, standing pig
    - Tan Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 26)
      Dark tan standing pig; unclear if made of ceramic
    - Green Resting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 29)
      Green, ceramic pig at rest
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 31)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with dark brown spots
    - Spotted Pig at Rest, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 32, 33)
      Gray and brown spotted pig at rest; ceramic
    - Pig by Change Purse, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 3)
      Pink pig by large, green change purse with gold detailing; ceramic
    - Yellowish Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 5)
      Yellowish, beige, ceramic, sitting pig; hollow
    - Pig with Pink Snout, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 13)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with gray spots and prominent pink snout
    - Cow-Like, Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 10)
      Cow-like, black and white spotted, standing, ceramic pig
    - Off-White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 15)
      Off-white pig with blue eyes and snout standing; ceramic
    - Off-White and Reddish-Brown Colored Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 19)
      Off-white and reddish-brown, ceramic pig
    - Dark Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 21)
      Very dark brown, ceramic pig; broken head and leg
    - White Pig with Bright Crest, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 22)
      White, ceramic pig with the text "Herne Bay" and a bright orange crest its back; gold features
    - Off-White and Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 24)
      Off-white and pink, ceramic pig with black eyes standing on hind legs
    - Beige Pig with Alert Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 1)
      Beige, ceramic pig sitting with upturned ears
    - Pig on Grass, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 10)
      Beige, ceramic pig resting on the grass
    - Pig with Gold Features, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 16)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with golden ears and trotters
    - Pink Pig with Crackle Pattern, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 17)
      Pink, hunched over, ceramic pig with crackle pattern all over
    - Pig with Blue Spots, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 19)
      Standing, white, ceramic pig with blue spots
    - Pig with Snout in the Grass, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 23)
      Beige, ceramic pig with its snout in the grass
    - Tan and White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 30)
      Tan and white, ceramic, standing pig
    - Pink and White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 31)
      Pink and white, ceramic, standing pig
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 33)
      Pink and white, ceramic, standing pig with tan spots
    - Gray Pig with Spots, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 38)
      Gray, ceramic pig with purplish-pink spots on its back
    - Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 39)
      Off-white and black, cow-like, ceramic pig
    - Pig on White Plate, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 41)
      Beige, ceramic pig on white plate with a blue motif
    - Pig in a Cup, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 42)
      White pig with gold detailing in a white cup that reads "Go Way Back, and Sit Down;" ceramic
    - Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 45)
      Ceramic pig with red detailing and floppy ears
    - Sitting, Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 46)
      Ceramic, sitting, off-white pig with black spots
    - Light Pink Sitting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 47)
      Ceramic, sitting, light pink pig with gray detailing
    - Light Pink and White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 50)
      Light pink and white, ceramic pig resting
    - Pig with Large Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 53)
      Ceramic, gray and white pig in motion; has large, upturned ears
    - Pig with Upturned Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 54)
      Ceramic pig with upturned ears sitting
    - Pig with Open Mouth, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 63)
      Resting, ceramic, beige-pink pig with open mouth; hollow figurine
    - Reddish-Tan Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 64)
      Reddish-tan standing pig with blue eyes
    - Sprawled Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 72)
      Ceramic pig with grey and charcoal detail standing with sprawled legs
    - Sitting Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 75)
      Gray and tan, ceramic pig sitting
    - White and Charcoal Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 2)
      White and charcoal-colored pig sitting
    - Round Pig on White Base, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 5)
      Round, pink, ceramic pig on white base
    - Black and Pink Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 6)
      Black and pink spotted, ceramic pig
    - Peach Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 17)
      Peach, ceramic pig standing
    - Pink, White, Charcoal and Beige-Colored Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 29)
      Pink, white, charcoal, and beige-colored, ceramic pig figurine
    - Clear Pig with Orange Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 31)
      Clear, ceramic pig with orange ears; damaged
    - Clear Pig with Pink Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 32)
      Clear, ceramic pig with pink ears
    - Ceramic Pig Head, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 37)
      Ceramic pig head showing teeth.
    - Ceramic, Sitting, Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 39)
      Ceramic, sitting, pink pig with tan detailing/shading on its back.
    - Black and Brown Warthog, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 43)
      Black and brown warthog; ceramic.
    - White Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 52)
      White standing pig with pink snout and inner ears.
  - Subseries I B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Human-Like Traits
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of ceramic material and are engaged in a human-like activity or display human-like behavior.
    - Disney Sailor Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 28)
      Ceramic pig dressed as a sailor in a black and white tee-shirt and yellow tee-shirt; "Disney" appears on object's reverse
    - Little Pig Robinson, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 28)
      Ceramic figurine of the characters from Beatrix Potter's The Tale of Little Pig Robinson.
    - Pig in Cap and Sweater, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 5)
      Ceramic pig wearing a burgundy newsboy cap and burgundy sweater with yellow patches
    - Pig Head in Renaissance Garb, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 6)
      Ceramic pig head dressed in a Renaissance-inspired purple hat, green necktie, and pinkish collar
    - Pig in Hat and Overalls, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 10)
      Ceramic pig wearing a red hat and red overalls with one undone strap
    - Pig with Blonde Hair and Clover Collar, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 29)
      Beige, ceramic pig figurine with green lips, green ears, clover collar, and a blonde patch of hair
    - Pig in Suit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 23)
      White, ceramic pig in white top hat and white suit
    - Sitting Pig Figurine with Gold Trotters, circa 1900-2013 (Box 3, Item 7)
      Dark beige pig with metallic gold trotters sitting upright on a beige base
    - Gray Sitting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 12)
      Gray sitting pig with light charcoal-colored shading
    - Pig with Book, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 15)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with charcoal-colored ears and blue shirt sitting on a pink stool reading a book
    - Pig with Baskets in Umbrella-Shaped Nook, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 14)
      Pink, ceramic pig with baskets in green, umbrella-shaped nook
    - Pig with Sleigh, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 16)
      Pink, ceramic pig on blue sleigh
    - Pig with Pillow, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 1)
      Honey brown, ceramic pig kneeling on pillow
    - Pig with Ball, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 4)
      Beige, ceramic pig with green bowtie holding a ball that reads "Alle Neune;" tape and tape residue present
    - Pig in Suit with Sack, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 8)
      Ceramic, white pig with metallic gold features in suitcoat and bowtie next to sack
    - Pig with Hat with Bow, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 12)
      Ceramic, off-white pig with blue and pink hat with bow
    - Pig Guiding Sleigh, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 14)
      Light pink, ceramic pig guiding a sleigh
    - Pig with Telephone, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 16)
      Pink, ceramic pig with old-fashioned telephone
    - Pig in Coin Purse, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 5)
      Ceramic, white pig in a green coin purse that reads "Pig in a Poke Just Off to Market"
    - Pig Mailing Letter, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 7)
      White, ceramic pig putting a letter into a green mailbox
    - Pig Playing a Pipe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 7)
      Off-white, ceramic pig with maroon detail playing a pipe
    - Pig with Binoculars, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 12)
      Pink, ceramic pig in bag using binoculars
    - Pig on Bench, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 16)
      Ceramic, pink pig sitting on a blue bench playing an instrument
    - Piglet in Crib, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 5)
      Pink, ceramic pig in crib with clover on side
    - Female Pig in Green Outfit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 20)
      Human-like, ceramic pig in green dress and green bow with blonde hair; meant to sit on a ledge or at the edge of a shelf
    - Pig in Suit Smoking and Reading, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 1)